{
    "subject": "resource/Steve_Lavin",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/San_Francisco,_California",
    "human_readable": "Steve Lavin was born in San Francisco, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8918737769126892,
            "question": "Where was Steve Lavin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.865394651889801,
            "question": "In what state was Steve Lavin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378685712814331,
            "question": "Name the city of Steve Lavin's birth."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7870397567749023,
            "question": "What year was Steve Lavin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5604237914085388,
            "question": "What is Steve Lavin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2911207675933838,
            "question": "Was Steve Lavin a successful coach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25513073801994324,
            "question": "Where did Steve Lavin coach at the professional level?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2098124623298645,
            "question": "Did Steve Lavin play professionally after college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15668129920959473,
            "question": "What position did Steve Lavin play in basketball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13062457740306854,
            "question": "What college did Steve Lavin play basketball for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steve Lavin was born in San Francisco, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2338_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Steve Lavin play in basketball?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2338_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Steve Lavin play professionally after college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2338_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Steve Lavin coach at the professional level?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2338_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2338_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Steve Lavin was born on September 4, 1964, in San Francisco, California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}